const lordRingsQuizData = [
    {
        QuizName: "Lord of the Rings"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "1",
        Question: "What is the name of the Hobbit that carries the ring most of the way in The Lord of the Rings?",
        Options: ["Merry", "Frodo", "Sam", "Pippin"],
        Answer: "Frodo"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "2",
        Question: "Which wizard accompanied the Fellowship on their travels in the Fellowship of the Ring?",
        Options: ["Saruman", "Gandalf", "Radagast", "Tom Bombadil"],
        Answer: "Gandalf"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "3",
        Question: "What is the name of Sauron's tower?",
        Options: ["Minas Tirith", "Minas Anor", "Orthanc", "Barad-dûr"],
        Answer: "Barad-dûr"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "4",
        Question: "How many members are in the Fellowship?",
        Options: ["8", "9", "6", "7"],
        Answer: "9"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "5",
        Question: "What is the name of the Ent that accompanies Merry and Pippin?",
        Options: ["Treebeard", "Beechbone", "Fimbrethil", "Finglas"],
        Answer: "Treebeard"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "6",
        Question: "Who was the last high king of the Noldor that served in Lindon?",
        Options: ["Finrod Felagund", "Gil-Galad", "Fingolfin", "Fëanor"],
        Answer: "Gil-Galad"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "7",
        Question: "What land did Sauron take for himself and rule from during the Third Age of Middle-Earth?",
        Options: ["The Shire", "Mordor", "Gondor", "Rhûn"],
        Answer: "Mordor"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "8",
        Question: "Who is Shelob's mother?",
        Options: ["Ungoliant", "Aragog", "Morgoth", "Éowyn"],
        Answer: "Ungoliant"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "9",
        Question: "What is the name of the older, white and male, tree that gave light to Arda in the Year of the Tree in Tolkien's legendarium?",
        Options: ["Laurelin", "Telperion", "Treebeard", "Yavanna"],
        Answer: "Telperion"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "10",
        Question: "What is the name of the younger, gold and female, tree that gave light to arda in the Year of the Tree in Tolkien's legendarium?",
        Options: ["Laurelin", "Telperion", "Ulmo", "Mandos"],
        Answer: "Laurelin"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "11",
        Question: "Morgoth was the original evil in Tolkien's legendarium. This was a name given to him by Fëanor to mean, 'Black Foe of the World.' What was his original name?",
        Options: ["Finwë", "Maedhros", "Melkor", "Tulkas"],
        Answer: "Melkor"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "12",
        Question: "Who was the second member of the Fellowship to die during the quest to destroy the One Ring?",
        Options: ["Gandalf", "Boromir", "Gimli", "Aragorn"],
        Answer: "Boromir"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "13",
        Question: "Mount Doom is the extremely popular volcano where the One Ring was created, and later destroyed. What is the Sindarin translation?",
        Options: ["Melon", "Orodruin", "Ephel Dúath", "Emyn Muil"],
        Answer: "Orodruin"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "14",
        Question: "There is a set of twin statues that the Fellowship sail by on their quest. What is the name of these statues?",
        Options: ["Argonath", "Enedwaith", "Minas Ithil", "Oromë"],
        Answer: "Argonath"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "15",
        Question: "Frodo and Sam, after leaving the rest of the Fellowship, encounter a creature. What is the name of this creature?",
        Options: ["Bilbo", "Fatty Bolger", "Gollum", "Déagol"],
        Answer: "Gollum"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "16",
        Question: "Sauron created many rings beyond his One Ring. among all of them, he created 9 for men. What did these men come to be known?",
        Options: ["Haradrim", "Easterlings", "Rohirrim", "Nazgûl"],
        Answer: "Nazgûl"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "17",
        Question: "Who is the god-like character in Tolkien's legendarium?",
        Options: ["Manwë", "Eru Ilúvatar", "Aulë", "Ulmo"],
        Answer: "Eru Ilúvatar"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "18",
        Question: "Which Valar created the dwarves in Tolkien's legendarium?",
        Options: ["Eru Ilúvatar", "Aulë", "Nienna", "Varda"],
        Answer: "Aulë"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "19",
        Question: "Morgoth was the strongest of the Valar before his downfall into darkness. Who then, after Morgoth, became the strongest of the Valar to be the mouth for Eru Ilúvatar?",
        Options: ["Estë", "Vairë", "Mandos", "Manwë"],
        Answer: "Manwë"
    },
    {
        QuestionNum: "20",
        Question: "There was a love story that was deeply personal to Tolkien. What two characters are in this story?",
        Options: ["Aragorn & Arwen", "Beren & Lúthien", "Faramir & Éowyn", "Samwise & Rosie"],
        Answer: "Beren & Lúthien"
    }
]